Kabir Kakkar

Currently working as a software engineer at Accenture, in the field of DevOps, and has experience with Terraform, AWS resources, Docker, Machine Learning, Power BI, MERN stack, Python, C++, Java, and Unity.

Contact No: (+91) 981-112-0224 Email: kabir.kakkar4@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/kabir
-kakkar/

Github:

https://github.com/kabir-kakkar

Online Portfolio:

https://kabir-kakkar.github.io/

EXPERIENCE

Accenture

Custom Software Engineering Associate

L2 LLP: November 2022 - Present • Full-Time

Worked with the client for handling their DevOps Department

Associate Software Engineer

ePlatform Management: May 2021 - October 2022 • Full-Time

Worked as a primary developer for the development of legacy code through Terraform, AWS Cloud Services and Docker.

Successfully developed 30+AWS Resources through Terraform.

Maintained 3 API and 1 UI URL with less than 1 day of down-time.

Resolved 50+ bug tickets

Celebal Technologies Associate Data Engineer

Jan 2020 - June 2020 • Internship

Made a machine learning model on Real-Time Demand Forecasting, using the Pyspark framework with Databricks and Microsoft Azure.

EDUCATION

Manipal University Jaipur, Rajasthan — B.Tech. in Computer and Communication Engineering

June 2017 - June 2021 • GPA: 8.1/10

GD Goenka Public School, Delhi— *Matriculation*.

May 2015 - May 2017

The Indian School, Delhi — *Matriculation*

May 2005 - May 2015

SKILLS

Programming Languages

C++, C, Python, Java

Web Development

HTML, CSS, React, Node.JS, MongoDB, SQL

AWS

Terraform

Power BI

Machine Learning

PUBLICATIONS

Implementation of Demand Forecasting – A Comparative Approach (See Publication) IOP Science Jan 18, 2021

CERTIFICATIONS

Machine Learning • (See Certificate)

Web Development • (See Certificate)

Unity • (See Certificate)

LANGUAGES

English

Hindi

French (Elementary Proficiency)

VOLUNTEER

Treasurer at Rotaract Green Club